说一件关于我们婚礼的事情
Some news of our wedding,
我给各位发了一封"空出时间"电邮
I have sent you all a "Save the date" e-mail.
太好啦  你们选好日子了吗
Oh, exciting. You guys picked a date?
何止如此  我选好了80个日子
Better. I picked 80 dates.
我需要你们空出全部日子  直到名单缩小
And I need you to save them all until we narrow it down.
我还以为我们同意选6月15了
I thought we agreed on June 15.
那是美国国旗日隔天
That's the day after Flag Day.
大家肯定庆祝到虚脱了
Everyone'll be partied out.
选个日子而已  干脆点
It's a date-- just pick one.
这不止是一个日子  这是经典的最佳化问题
It's not just a date-- it's a textbook optimization problem.
绝对有个最佳日期  就像是有
There is a perfect date-- just like there's
最佳室温与最佳餐后甜品一样
a perfect room temperature and a perfect dessert.
才没有最佳餐后甜品呢
Mm. There's no perfect dessert.
恐龙形状的海绵蛋糕
Yellow cake in the shape of a dinosaur
撒上巧克力糖霜
with chocolate frosting,
边上配一勺香草冰淇淋球
a scoop of vanilla ice cream on the side,
不碰到蛋糕
not touching.
到时候你就知道了
You'll see.
你会在我们婚礼上吃到
You'll have it at our wedding.
来打赌吗
You wanna bet?
你们给我足够时间
You give me enough time,
我也能够为婚礼算出完美日子
I can do the same thing with a wedding date--
它必须是在周末
it needs to be on the weekend,
避开你们任何人的生日
uh, not near any of your birthdays,
或漫展周末
or the weekend of Comic Con.
你也可以在漫展上结婚啊
Ooh, you could get married at Comic Con.
-不行  -不行
- No! - No!
我们只需要选一个
We just need a weekend date
无聊又平凡的普通周末就行了
that's completely boring and uneventful.
让你们不把事情都安排好
Too bad you didn't get your ducks in a row,
不然其实今晚完美符合你条件呢
'cause tonight would have been perfect.
第十一季  第三集
早安
Good morning.
早安啊
我知道今天是吃苹果脆片的日子  但没有了
I know today is Apple Jacks day, but... we're all out.
没事  我吃什么都行
That's fine. I'll have anything.
真的假的
Really?
是啊  你懂的
Yeah. You know...
无所...
whatev.
"无所[谓]"吗
"Whatev"?
我喜欢你的这面
I like this side of you.
那你知道我喜欢什么吗
You know what I like?
柔和爵士
Smooth jazz.
Feels so good - Chuck Mangione
提醒你一下
Hey, just a reminder--
-今天下班后我要去喝酒  -很好
- I'm going out for drinks after work. - Oh. Great.
提醒你一下  你有孕在身
Just a reminder-- you're pregnant.
我自己不喝  只是带新同事去
I'm not drinking, just taking a new coworker out.
提醒你一下  你是有夫之妇
Oh. Just a reminder-- you're married.
女同事
Female coworker.
初来乍到  我想让她感觉有家的温暖
She's new in town, and I want to make her feel welcome.
以及在大家跟她说我很毒辣之前
And let her know the office is full of liars
先灌输她办公室都是说谎精的思想
before everyone tells her I'm mean.
她单身吗
Is she single?
我才不要撮合她跟拉杰
I'm not setting her up with Raj.
-那斯图尔特呢  -你是没听我说话吗
- What about Stuart? - Are you listening?
我想要她觉得我是暖心好人
I want her to think I'm not mean.
好吧  我会这么说
Okay. Well, it's just...
也只是因为我们有两个单身朋友嘛
we have two single friends.
华仔  我才刚认识这女生
Howie, I just met this woman.
何不稍微等到我更了解她之后呢
Why don't I wait a little and get to know her?
或许我会讨厌她  到时我就会很乐意
Maybe I won't like her, and then I'd be happy
让斯图尔特与拉杰毁了她人生
to ruin her life with Stuart or Raj.
这样我就满足了
That's all I ask.
你们俩跟谢尔顿同住过很长一段时间
So, you guys lived with Sheldon for a long time...
-好长  -太长了
- Long time. - So very long.
对了  再次恭喜你们订婚啊
By the way, congratulations again on your engagement.
对啊  你找到了人中之龙啊
Yeah. You got a good one.
谢谢  所以有件怪事
Thanks. So, it's strange,
谢尔顿昨晚睡觉说梦话了
Sheldon was talking in his sleep last night,
感觉他完全是另一个人
and he seemed like a totally different person.
他很放松而且...
He was relaxed and...
散漫且平静
loose and calm.
谢尔顿是个复杂的男人
Well, Sheldon's a complicated man.
他说了"无所"
He said "Whatev."
带他去做大脑扫描  可能长脑瘤了
Give him a brain scan-- that might be a tumor.
我觉得计划婚礼对他造成太大压力了
Well, I think the wedding planning is really stressful for him,
从而导致梦呓
and that can trigger sleep talking.
或许那是谢尔顿性格中
Well, maybe this is a part of Sheldon's personality
一直被他压抑的一部分
he's been repressing.
毕竟不是正所谓
I mean, I think we dream about things
日有所思夜有所梦吗
we wish we could be in real life.
是吗  那你都梦些什么了
Really? What do you dream about?
比如当莱纳德的老婆
Oh. Uh... being the wife of Leonard.
基本都是这个啦
Mostly that.
我选择相信你
I choose to believe you.
虽然人类对大脑做过无数研究
Well, as much as we've studied the brain,
但人类对梦与它的作用还是有许多不了解
there's still a lot we don't know about dreams and their function.
心理学家们对它的解读也有分歧
You know, even psychologists are divided on it.
的确  佛洛依德认为梦与性有关
Mm, it's true-- Freud thought dreams were about sex,
两者曾是同一精神分析学会的核心人物  后者不同意前者看法  因此退出并自成一派
阿德勒认为梦与支配有关
Adler thought they were about dominance...
再次强调  我的梦都是与嫁给这位小巨人有关
Then again, mine are just about being married to this little guy.
这次感觉像是在嘲讽我了
Well, now it's just edging into mockery.
搬到新的城市真的有些让人害怕
Well, moving to a new city was a little scary,
但这份工作感觉挺不错的
but the job seems great.
大家人都很好
Everyone's really nice.
是啊  都超好
Oh, they are. Super nice.
虽然只有一个人晚上带你出来玩
I mean, only one them took you out tonight--
但毕竟这也不是什么比赛
but it's not a competition.
再次谢谢你
Thanks again.
其实我们可以去更适合孕妇的地方啊
You know, we could have gone somewhere more pregnancy-friendly.
没事的  怀孕的其中一个亮点就是
Oh, it's okay. One of the great things about being pregnant
可以用酒杯喝蔓越莓汁
is drinking cranberry juice out of a wineglass
然后看别人着急的反应
and watching people freak out.
妮妮
Bernie!
我勒个去
Oh, damn.
有缘千里来相会啊
Hey! What are the odds?
是啊  真特么"巧"啊
Yeah, seren-frickin'-dipity.
你好
Hello.
-拉杰什  -斯图尔特
- Rajesh. - Stuart.
我叫如琪
Hi. Ruchi.
如琪是我的同事
Ruchi is my coworker.
但估计你们在介绍简报里都看过了
But that was probably in your briefing packet.
怎么啦
What's wrong?
我找到了最佳的结婚日了
Well, I found the perfect wedding date.
-那太棒啦  -才不呢
- That's terrific! - No, it's not.
是1996年5月19日
It was May 19, 1996.
我们本来可以有一场完美的婚礼
We would have had a lovely wedding.
我们的蜜月之旅刚好还能对上
And our honeymoon would have coincided
该彗星在1995年被发现  于1997年4月1日过近日点
海尔-波普彗星的首次出现
with the first appearance of the Hale-Bopp comet.
谢尔顿  你当时才16岁
Sheldon, you were 16.
那时我也还在德州  我们那里才没人会管
And in Texas-- no one would have batted an eye.
等等  那天也不好
Oh, wait, it's no good.
第三任《神秘博士》演员是在那天去世的
That's the day that Jon Pertwee, the third Doctor Who, died.
而且那天已经过了
And it's in the past.
我已经说那天不好了  放下吧
Hey-hey, I said it's no good-- just let it go.
谢尔顿
Sheldon...
我很感激你想让婚礼完美的心
I appreciate you trying to make this wedding perfect,
但这都快把你搞疯了
but it's making you miserable.
不是  婚礼没有要把我搞疯
No, the wedding isn't making me miserable,
是日子
the calendar is.
为什么名人就不能集中在
Why can't there just be one week each month
每个月某周去世呢
for famous people to die?
外国的一种迷信  有人认为一个人死去后  会有另外两个与死者有关系的人也跟着过世
都已经丧事成三了
Well, they've already arranged to die in threes--
你还想要求人家怎么样啊
what more do you want from them?
真是闹心  为什么我就找不出最佳的日子呢
This is so frustrating. Why can't I find a perfect date?
我就找出了与牛仔打招呼的最佳方式啊
I found the perfect way to say hi to cowboys.
我只是觉得或许在你内心的深处
I'm just saying maybe there's a part of you deep down that...
有一部分的你只想放松下来
just wants to relax a little, you know?
逍遥一点
Kick back.
比如说出"无所..."
Say, "Whatev."
无所...吗
Whatev?
抱歉  你真的不把那词说完吗
I'm sorry, you're really not gonna finish that word?
我只是举个例子嘛
I-I'm just trying to make a point...
说完它  艾米
Finish the word, Amy.
行  谓
Fine. Er.
谓  谓  谓
Er, er, er.
谢谢
Thank you.
但你现在欠我三次"无所"了
Only now you owe me three more whatevs.
原来你是印度特里凡得琅出生的啊
Oh, you were born in Trivandrum.
你去过那里的百马宫了吗
Have you ever been to the Kuthira Malika Palace?
没  没去过呢
No, I haven't.
我也是呢  真是太有缘了
Me, either. What a small world.
我也没去过那里
I've also never been there.
我没去过的地方太多了
I've never been lots of places.
来啊  考我看看
Go on, quiz me.
对不起  我们这么聊印度的事太无礼了
I'm sorry, we're being rude talking about India.
是啊  如果你跟伯纳黛特
Oh, yeah, you know, if you and Bernadette
想聊美国的事  我们没意见的
want to talk about America, that's cool with us.
我来帮你们起个头吧
Here, let me get you started.
汉堡包  对吧
Hamburgers. Am I right?
你们都做什么工作
So, what do you guys do?
我是个天体物理学家
Well, I am an astrophysicist,
如果你哪天晚上出去看仰望星空
so if you ever go out at night and look up at the stars,
也能算是看入我的办公室呢
that's kind of my office.
他卖漫画书给孩子
He sells comic books to children.
其实呢
Actually,
我是自己开的店
I own my own store.
如果你有兴趣来看看
Uh, I-if you'd like to check it out sometime,
我最近在做个促销活动
I'm running a new promotion--
买任何东西  就请你吃价钱合理的晚餐一次
buy anything, get taken out for a reasonably priced dinner.
是啊  斯图尔特经济上有些困难
Yeah, yeah, Stuart's struggling financially.
但他并没有因此被击垮
But he doesn't let that get him down.
他对自己有信心
He believes in himself.
尽管全世界都清楚地告诉他
Even though the whole world has made it clear
他不该盲目自信
he should not.
谢谢你啊
Thank you.
对了  拉杰  我觉得你现在
A-And, you know, Raj, I think it's great
再也不像个被宠坏的米虫一样靠父母吃饭
that you no longer live off your parents like a spoiled child.
而是去住别人家车库  就像个...
You live over someone's garage like a...
成年废柴
failed adult.
是啊  你还跟她同住呢
Yeah, well, you live with her.
不是那样的
Oh, it's not like that.
他跟我们夫妇租了一间房
He rents a room from me and my husband.
我们也是无妄之灾啊
Who, by the way, is no prize, either.
我才不在意
Oh, I don't care.
你懂我  我随波逐流
You know me-- I just go with the flow.
海滩  公共泳池
Beach, public pool...
听起来都超赞
They both sound awesome.
回头想想  海滩
On second thought, beach.
我想跟海鸥交朋友
I'd like to befriend a seagull.
简直不敢相信
That is crazy.
对啊  你能发一份到我邮箱吗
Yeah. Will you e-mail that to me?
你有播过这个给他听吗
Have you played this for him?
没有  我怕他说我侵犯他隐私权
No. I'm worried he'll say I violated his privacy.
你们听他有多开心
Listen how happy he sounds.
做什么都可以
I'm up for anything,
只要在你身边就行
as long as I'm with you.
-你们在听什么  -没什么
- What are you listening to? - Nothing.
干嘛藏着  我也想听
Oh, come on, I want to hear.
我们才不需要导航
We don't need GPS.
路长在脚下  我们只需随心而行
Let's just see where the road takes us.
难怪你们刚才要关掉
I see why you turned it off.
这人听起来就像个傻逼
That guy sounds like an idiot.
亲爱的  那人就是你
Honey, that's you.
别傻了  我的声音又深沉又响亮
Don't be silly. My voice is deep and sonorous.
美国知名演员  为《星球大战》系列电影中的黑武士配音
就像白人版的詹姆斯·厄尔·琼斯
Like a Caucasian James Earl Jones.
"卢克  我是你爹"  听见没
"Luke, I am your father." See?
真的是你
It is you.
我在你睡觉时录的
I recorded you in your sleep.
看啊  一个搭便车的人
Oh, look-- a hitchhiker.
我猜他一定有些有趣的故事
I bet he has some interesting stories.
那是我吗
That's me?
是你
It's you.
你暗中监视我睡觉吗
So you spied on me in my sleep?
谢尔顿  我不是故意的
Sheldon, I'm sorry.
你每晚都这么说梦话
You've been doing this every night.
我不禁好奇这些梦话是否代表什么
I couldn't help but wonder if it meant something.
并没有
Well, it doesn't.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
前额皮质掌管自控力
I mean, the prefrontal cortex regulates impulse control.
所以我们睡着时  平时被压抑的个性
So it's plausible that when we're asleep,
可能会跑出来这种理论是说得通的
aspects of our personality that we repress might come out.
别以为加了科学词  屁话就不是屁话了
Don't try to put science lipstick on your New Age pig!
声明一下
And for the record,
你睡觉时也发出声音
you make noises when you sleep,
我可从没说过你压抑了心中的电锯
and I've never accused you of repressing your inner chainsaw.
婚礼证婚时会询问  有没有人反对这婚事
如果你想让我在婚礼上提出反对
If you want me to object at your wedding,
给我打个暗号就行
just give me one of these.
漫威漫画《神奇四侠》中的角色
这个行星吞噬者正在吞噬星球的画面
This picture of Galactus eating a planet looks like
就像我的孕妻在吞食咖啡蛋糕的样子
my preggo wife destroying a coffee cake.
是啊  是有点像
Oh, yeah, I see it.
我只是说  你应该退出
I'm just saying, you should bow out.
为什么是我该退出
Why should I bow out?
因为我们都知道结局会如何
Uh, because we all know how this is gonna end.
我的医生也这么说  但我还在这活蹦乱跳呢
That's what my doctor said, too, but I'm still here.
听着  我觉得我和她有更多共同点
Okay, look, I think that she and I have more in common.
因为你们都是印度人吗
Because you're Indian?
就因为她是棕色人种  你就可以和她约会了
So just 'cause she's brown, you get to date her?
是啊
Yes!
下次我们遇到一个
And the next time we meet a woman
皮肤苍白得像死尸的女人  她就归你了
who's pale and cadaver-like, she's all yours.
霍华德  伯纳黛特昨晚在场
Howard, Bernadette was there last night.
她回家后有说什么吗
Did she say anything when she got home?
她说"你为什么告诉那俩白痴我在哪
Yeah, she said, "Why'd you tell those idiots where I was?
谢你一辈子啊"
Thanks a lot."
好吧  我们掷硬币决定怎么样
Okay, how about we flip a coin?
等等  那女生对此事不该有发言权吗
Look, hang on. Doesn't this girl get a word in all of this?
她不是该发言表示"不要"吗
And isn't that word "No"?
如琪说想跟我们两个一起出来玩
Ruchi said she wanted to hang out with both of us.
我们何不就那么做吗
Why don't we just do that?
好吧  大家像朋友一样出去玩  顺其自然
Oh, fine. Let's hang out as friends and see what happens.
对啊  要是真滋生出什么  到时再担心吧
Yeah, and if something grows out of it, just worry about it then.
我的医生也是这么说的
Also what my doctor said.
今晚不是你的洗衣日啊
Hey, this isn't your laundry night.
就是啊  周三洗衣服
I know. Laundry on a Wednesday.
我的人生已经疯狂到这地步了
It's the madness my life has become.
你为什么会对说梦话这事烦恼呢
Why is this sleep-talking thing bothering you anyway?
很简单
It's simple.
我不喜欢
I don't like the idea
我的脑子也许对我隐瞒了另一种人格的可能
that my mind might be keeping an entire personality from me.
杰基尔博士的另一重人格可是海德先生
Dr. Jekyll's other personality was Mr. Hyde.
小说《化身博士》中的人物  杰基尔和海德代表了善与恶两种性格
海德"先生"啊
Mr. Hyde.
他连研究生学位都没有
Didn't have a postgraduate degree.
有没有可能你压力大
Is it possible that you're stressed
是因为你害怕结婚
because you're scared about getting married?
这是个大改变
I mean, it is a big change,
而你连个小改变都难以接受
and you're not good with little changes.
你胡说
Well, that's nonsense.
举个我对小改变不开心的例子
You name one little change I was upset with.
他们把绿色彩虹糖的口味从青柠改成了苹果
Uh, when they changed the green Skittle from lime to apple.
那不是人家从小吃的彩虹
That is not the rainbow I grew up tasting.
好吧  重新来过
All right, fine. Let's start over.
说梦话会不会是你的大脑在告诉你
Is it possible that the sleep-talking is a part of your brain
一切都会很好
that's telling you everything's gonna be okay
你放松一点就行了
and you just need to relax a little?
所以你是在说自我只是幻觉
So you're proposing that the self is an illusion,
人其实有多个意识集合
and that we actually have multiple centers of consciousness
它们在相互交流吗
that are communicating with one another?
用非专业术语来说  是的
In laymen's terms, yeah.
有意思
Huh. Interesting.
所以你不认为有个笛卡尔自我
So you don't believe there's a Cartesian self
在经历流之下吗
that underlies the flux of experience?
二十几岁时可能信过  现在不信了
Maybe in my twenties, not anymore.
好吧  假定你说的是对的
Okay. Well, assuming you're right,
你会建议我怎么做
what would you suggest I do?
我会建议你先从一些小改变做起
Well, I would start with something small,
看会不会改善你的生活
see if it makes your life any better.
你可以学冥想  上瑜伽课
Um, you can learn to meditate, take a yoga class.
我倒是一直对人字拖感到好奇
Oh. You know, I have always been intrigued by flip-flops.
悠闲之人的标配鞋
The official footwear of the laid-back fellow.
你高兴就好
Okay, sure.
当然了  如果我的脚要暴露在外
Of course if my feet are gonna be exposed,
我就得去打新的破伤风疫苗
I'll need to update my tetanus booster.
有道理
Oh, yeah. Makes sense.
既然都去了  不如把流感疫苗也打了
Yeah. And while I'm there, I may as well get a flu shot
-再检查下痣  -好啊
- and a mole check. - Sure.
身上的痣产生奇异的变化  有可能是黑色素瘤
我还从来没检查过痣呢
You know, I've never had a mole check.
此生能认识你真好
Well, it's been nice knowing you.
给你
Here you go.
谢谢
Thanks.
斯图尔特来不了真可惜  感觉他挺有趣的
It's too bad Stuart couldn't make it. He seemed fun.
确实是的  我非常喜欢他
Oh, yeah, he is. I love him dearly, yeah.
倒不是说我不担心他
Not to say that I don't worry about him.
担心他什么
What's to worry about?
其实呢
You know what?
我说得太多了[学校]
I'm talking out of school.
性侵犯不能住在学校300米范围内
说起这个  他现在又能合法地住在学校附近了
Speaking of which, he's allowed to live near them now.
二位
Hey, guys.
-太好了  斯图尔特你来了  -是啊  斯图尔特
- Oh, great, Stuart. You're here. - Yeah, Stuart.
对呀   我都没想到你能来呢
Yeah, I did... I didn't think you were gonna make it.
你这话我信
Mm. I believe that.
抱歉  工作上的事  我得接一下
Sorry, guys. It's work. I've got to take it.
真高兴你能来  斯图尔特
I'm so glad you made it, Stuart.
没错  高兴死了
Oh, yeah, so glad.
真不敢相信你居然出阴招
I can't believe you went behind my back!
这就表明我比你更急切呀
Which clearly means I want this more!
你想和我比"谁更想脱单"吗
You want to play a game of "Who's more desperate" with me?
那你面对的可是大联盟级别选手哦  小伙子
'Cause you're in the big leagues now, Bucko.
如琪和我真的很有火花
L-Look, Ruchi and I are really hitting it off.
拜托你就把她让给我吧
Please let me just have this one!
老子哪都不去
I'm not going anywhere.
我就是那种治不好的真菌感染
I'm like a fungus you can't get rid of.
抱歉
Sorry.
你们在聊什么呢
So what's going on?
你正好错过了斯图尔特刚才在聊
Oh, you just missed Stuart's funny story
他那治不好的真菌感染
about the fungus he can't get rid of.
拉杰根本没通知我今晚的活动
Raj didn't tell me about tonight
好跟你独处
so he could be alone with you.
真的吗
Really?
这样有一点小变态啊
That's a little weird.
只有一点吗  这我还能改啊
Just a little? Because I can work with that.
两位  我暂时没打算谈恋爱
Look, guys, I'm not interested in dating anyone right now.
我只是想多认识一些朋友
I'm just looking to make some friends.
我完全理解你
Yeah, I totally understand.
但如果让你选个交往对象
But if you were gonna date someone,
你会选我还是斯图尔特呢
would it be me or Stuart?
我想我还是先走了
I think I'm gonna go.
如琪  对不起
Uh, uh, uh, uh, Ruchi, I'm sorry.
如果你还想以朋友身份一起玩  我很愿意
If you still want to hang out as friends, I'd like that.
谢了  斯图尔特  我也很愿意
Thanks, Stuart. I'd like that, too.
那小真菌就躲在你脚趾甲缝里
And the fungus is under the toenail.
回来了
Hello.
那个...  我...
So, um, I, uh...
我去穿了人字拖
I got flip-flops.
很好啊
Good for you.
我的妈呀  出什么事了
Oh, my God, what happened?!
我穿上人字拖后
After I got the flip-flops,
我发现脚背都暴露在外了
I realized that the tops of my feet were exposed, so, um,
于是我赶紧擦了防晒霜
I-I put on some sunscreen,
结果两只脚都滑腻腻的
which caused my feet to become slippery.
不出所料  一只拖鞋从我脚上滑飞
And predictably, one of them fell off
直接掉进了下水道口
and went down a sewer grate.
按我平常的脾气  我会一走了之
Now, normally, I would have walked away,
但作为一个全新  放松的我
but this is a new, laid-back me, so,
我没有生气  而是趴下去捡鞋
instead of getting upset, I just reached down to grab it.
然后我就摸到了某种毛茸茸的东西
That's when I touched something furry...
我说服自己那只是一顶湿假发
...which I'm telling myself was a damp toupee.
但当假发开始舔我的手时
When the toupee licked my hand...
我尖叫着
...I screamed
单脚穿着拖鞋跳走了
and hopped down the street on my remaining flip-flop.
-我可以问问...  -不  这故事还长着呢
- Can I just ask... - No, this is a long story.
不如把问题留到最后再问吧
Why don't we please save your questions till the end?
我后来发现了一张公车站的长凳
So, I-I finally came upon a bus bench
我在那里脱掉了我的一件衣服
where I sat and removed one of my shirts
用它做了一只临时的鞋
and, uh, fashioned it into a makeshift shoe.
这鞋不防水
Not a waterproof shoe.
这个细节和我接下来的故事大有关联
That is relevant to the next part of my story.
那是一坑深及脚踝的"温热金黄苹果汁"
The ankle-deep puddle of warm apple juice.
什么苹果汁
Apple juice?
也许是  也许不是
Maybe, maybe not.
我说服了自己好多事  艾米
I'm telling myself a lot of things, Amy.
那你剩下的那只人字拖去哪里了
What happened to your other flip-flop?
那个就涉及到一块我说服自己是
Oh, well, that involves what I am telling myself was a...
融化的巧克力棒的东西了
melted candy bar.
好吧  太心疼你了
Okay. I-I'm sorry.
我能帮你做点什么吗
Is there anything I can do to help?
有  我希望由你来负责我们的婚礼
Yes. I want you to be in charge of our wedding.
只需把地点和时间告诉我
Just you tell me where and when,
我会佩着胸花
and I will show up with a boutonniere
穿着不露脚趾的鞋子
and close-toed shoes and a...
还有晚礼服下的《星际迷航》制服来参加
a Star Trek uniform underneath my tuxedo.
最后这部分绝对没得商量
That last part is non-negotiable.
你确定这是你想要的吗
Are you sure that's what you want?
就像我打算在洗手液里泡澡一样确定
As sure as I'm about to go bathe in Purell.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
- I love you. - I love you, too.
我从小姑娘开始
You know, ever since I was a young girl,
就一直梦想着一场六月的婚礼
I-I've dreamed of a June wedding,
也许是在可以看到海边夕阳的悬崖边上
maybe on a cliff overlooking the ocean at sunset.
好呀
Sure.
听起来很不错
Sounds wonderful.
现在请允许我去清洗一下
Now, if you'll excuse me, I'm going to go clean up.
露天婚礼
Outdoor wedding.
我知道我会用那悬崖来干什么
I know what I'll be using that cliff for.
我宣布现在召开谢尔顿理事会常务会议
I call this meeting of the Council of Sheldons to order.
开始点名
Let's take roll.
科学谢尔顿
Science Sheldon?
到
Present.
德州谢尔顿
Texas Sheldon?
在这嘎达
Howdy.
狂热粉丝谢尔顿
Fanboy Sheldon?
向你问好
Greetings.
洁癖谢尔顿
Germaphobe Sheldon?
说话别喷口水
Say it, don't spray it.
运动员谢尔顿去哪里了
Where is Jock Sheldon?
现在别开玩笑  搞笑谢尔顿
Not the time, humorous Sheldon.
新的议题
Ok, new business.
我们是否同意授予懒散谢尔顿一个理事会席位
Do we grant layback Sheldon a seat on the council?
随便你们吧
Hey, whatever you guys want.
美国民谣歌手  获得16年诺贝尔文学奖后  拖了很久才去领奖
我和鲍勃·迪伦一样无所谓
I'm just chill like Bob Dylan.
拒绝
Negative.
没门
Heck no!
我感觉不舒服
I don't feel well.
我们能把他也踢走吗
Can we kick him out too?